[{"answer": "An action to take like this has to be -- it has to be some form of hate.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 3, "question": "Is it a hate crime?", "qSentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yes, I think my first reaction was, to be honest with you, I could guess, you know, it was a case of mistaken identity.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Do you -- have you felt like you've been vulnerable?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "What is your reaction to that statement from the family of the man that committed this terrible atrocity?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "I think there's no question about it at all.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Do you believe that this kind of extremism, the white supremacy, but also other forms of extremism, is that on the increase in America, do you believe?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "My best guess is that he's a fool.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "I mean what do you imagine may have been given what you know about his background, his motivation here?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "As I recall he was a bright, intelligent, and very kind individual.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "What is your recollection of the kind of man that Wade Michael Page was?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Back then, as far as he was concerned, it was just anybody that wasn't white.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "I mean, who were the targets of this holy war as far as he was concerned?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Basically, it was just -- he had gotten drunk the night before and showed up at morning formation intoxicated, and that just started the ball rolling to get him moved out of the military.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Do you know what the details of that misconduct were?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Honestly, I don't think he would have tried to distinguish.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Would he have tried to distinguish between the two groups?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "No, I knew that it wasn't just talk, that he had fallen deeper into whatever group he had gotten himself mixed up with.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Did you come away from that encounter thinking that he was now dangerous and that this was not just talk?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Piers, what is really interesting is that my comment that guns don't belong in the civil society generated so much hostility, anger, rage, ethnocentrism, bigotry, prejudice, and racism.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "What is the practical thing that can be done now?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Is there so many gun murders as a matter of routine every day, every week, every month, every year?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "He probably assumed that anyone with a beard or a turban is probably from the Taliban.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "-- fears that maybe it was deliberately targeted at the Sikh community?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "RANKLIN: Just complete shock.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "What was your reaction when that happened to someone so close to you?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "What are you, 17?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Oh my gosh, without a doubt.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "It must feels slightly surreal, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Are you all buddies?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "My question for you is you could go to a desert island with one of two men, Ryan Lochte or Michael Phelps, for the rest of your life, who would it be?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Because I am all about the team.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Why have you done that?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I have no idea yet.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Where are you going?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Probably not.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Harvard?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "I certainly don't think so.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Do you believe that the achievements of the Jamaican team should be viewed without any suspicion?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Yes --", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Do I look gangster?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Gosh, I can't sit here and not say Michael Phelps.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Who has excited you most watching the other sports?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "I was going to get to him too.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "What about Usain Bolt last night?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "And more importantly, to be sitting here with me again?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "About 2008, she was about 11, she started saying, mom, I think that I can do this.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Take me back to that decision?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "AWKINS: Or that too.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Or she's finding a new mother?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "She glows when she smiles and she's a doll to be around.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "When she first arrived, what was your first impression?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "For me, it was just total elation, because I knew what had gone into making that dream come true.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "What was the moment like when she won gold?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Just so proud of her, to again make all the sacrifices that she made at such a young age, and then go out and live her dream and at the same time representing her country.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Missy, for you?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "That was ridiculous, didn't you think?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Could you ever imagine in your wildest dreams this was going to happen to your little girl?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "Right now, we're taking our time to see which brands most are compatible with what she wants to personify.", "docId": "120806pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "How are you going to keep her under control?", "qSentId": 608}]